{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Custom Cabinet Makers \u0026 Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40624/":{"taskOID":40624,"originalTaskOID":40624,"setID":5589,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500120,"questionDisplayText":"Describe your cabinet project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your cabinet project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes your cabinet project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200180,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install new custom cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new custom cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20499,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Refinish existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Refinish existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20500,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reface existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Reface existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500102,"questionDisplayText":"Location of cabinets","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the location of the cabinets:","shortQuestionText":"Select the location of the cabinets:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500120,"questionDisplayText":"Describe your cabinet project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes your cabinet project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes your cabinet project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200180,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install new custom cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new custom cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20499,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Refinish existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Refinish existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20500,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reface existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Reface existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200440,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new pre-made cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200181,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200180,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install new custom cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Install new custom cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20499,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Refinish existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Refinish existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20500,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reface existing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Reface existing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500101,"questionDisplayText":"Part of larger remodel","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this project part of a larger remodel?","shortQuestionText":"Part of larger remodel?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500102,"questionDisplayText":"Location of cabinets","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the location of the cabinets:","shortQuestionText":"Select the location of the cabinets:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40624/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40624,"taskName":"Custom Cabinets - Build","taskDescription":"Build Custom Cabinets","xmTaskDescriptor":"Custom Cabinet Makers \u0026 Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5118,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"custom cabinet cabinetry pantry vanity","textMessagingName":"Custom Cabinet","rolloverLongDesc":"Builds cabinets from scratch to precisely fit the space \u0026 the customer's needs, both functional \u0026 aesthetic. Emphasis is on high quality \u0026 custom work, not low price.","rolloverShortDesc":"Skilled woodworker for custom cabinets.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build Custom Cabinets.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Custom Cabinet Makers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build Kitchen Cabinets","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Custom Cabinets","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Custom Cabinets - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Custom Cabinets Builder Need","urlName":"Custom-Cabinets-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Custom Cabinet Makers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs, Reviews | Build Kitchen Cabinets","searchKeywords":"custom,cabinet,cabinetry,pantry,vanity,storage,bathroom,kitchen,garage","emcCategoryOid":-12009,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":5589,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}